Guide to the Office of Public Affairs, Yale University, Photographs of Individuals
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Photographs of Individuals, 1870-1972; Series I
  - Celento, William (Box 14, Folder 545)
  - Cestaro, Mario (Box 14, Folder 546)
  - Chaet, Bernard R. (Box 14, Folder 547)
  - Chaffee, John (Box 14, Folder 548)
  - Chagall, Marc (Box 14, Folder 549)
  - Chaliapin, ----- (Box 14, Folder 550)
  - Chamberlain, Gordon (Box 14, Folder 551)
  - Chamberlain, Neil W. (Box 14, Folder 552)
  - Chambers, Robert (III) (Box 14, Folder 553)
  - Chambers, Wick (Box 14, Folder 554)
  - Champa, Kermit S. (Box 14, Folder 555)
  - Chandler, John R. (Box 14, Folder 556)
  - Chang, Kwang-Chih (Box 14, Folder 557)
  - Chapin, Lebeus C. (Box 14, Folder 558)
  - Chapin, Melville (Box 14, Folder 559)
  - Chapman, Edward M. (Box 14, Folder 560)
  - Chapman, Gilbert (Box 14, Folder 561)
  - Chapman, Herman H. (Box 15, Folder 562)
  - Chapman, S. Hartwell (Box 15, Folder 563)
  - Chappell, Thomas Huntington (Box 15, Folder 564)
  - Chardiet, Armando (Box 15, Folder 565)
  - Charpentier, Arthur Aldrich (Box 15, Folder 566)
  - Chase, Elizabeth A. (Box 15, Folder 567)
  - Chatfield, Barbara N. (Box 15, Folder 568)
  - Chauncey, Henry Jr. (Box 15, Folder 569)
  - Chermayeff, Serge (Box 15, Folder 570)
  - Chester, Colby (Box 15, Folder 571)
  - Chester, John (Box 15, Folder 572)
  - Child, Irvin L. (Box 15, Folder 573)
  - Childs, Barney (Box 15, Folder 574)
  - Ching, Julia C. (Box 15, Folder 575)
  - Chirelstein, Marvin A. (Box 15, Folder 576)
  - Chisolm, Lawrence (Box 15, Folder 577)
  - Chittenden, Russell (Box 15, Folder 578)
  - Christian, William A. (Box 15, Folder 579)
  - Chu, Boa-Teh (Box 15, Folder 580)
  - Chubb, Hendon (Box 15, Folder 581)
  - Church, Howard W. (Box 15, Folder 582)
  - Clapp, E. J. (Box 15, Folder 583)
  - Clark, Blair (Box 15, Folder 584)
  - Clark, Burton R. (Box 15, Folder 585)
  - Clark, Charles H. (19th C.) (Box 15, Folder 586)
  - Clark, Charles H. (20th C.) (Box 15, Folder 587)
  - Clark, Elias (Box 15, Folder 588)
  - Clark, Henry T. Jr. (Box 15, Folder 589)
  - Clark, Howard L. (Box 15, Folder 590)
  - Clark, Jack A. (Box 15, Folder 591)
  - Clark, John (Box 15, Folder 592)
  - Clark, Joseph (Box 15, Folder 593)
  - Clark, R. Inslee Jr. (Box 15, Folder 594)
  - Clark, Ramsey (Box 15, Folder 595)
  - Clark, Robert Charles (Box 15, Folder 596)
  - Clark, Steve (Box 15, Folder 597)
  - Clark, Sydney P. Jr. (Box 15, Folder 598)
  - Clark, Tom (Box 15, Folder 599)
  - Clarke, James G. (Box 15, Folder 600)
  - Clarke, William B. (Box 15, Folder 601)
  - Clay, Cassius (Box 15, Folder 602)
  - Clay, Clement C. (Box 15, Folder 603)
  - Clemence, Gerald M. (Box 15, Folder 604)
  - Clement, Stuart H. (Box 15, Folder 605)
  - Clifford, Clark (Box 15, Folder 606)
  - Clifford, Donald K. (Box 15, Folder 607)
  - Cliffton, E. Everett (Box 15, Folder 608)
  - Clift, David H. (Box 15, Folder 609)
  - Cochran, Gill (Box 16, Folder 610)
  - Cockroft, John (Sir) (Box 16, Folder 611)
  - Codlin, Kenneth E. (Box 16, Folder 612)
  - Coe, Buckner (Box 16, Folder 613)
  - Coe, Edward B. (Box 16, Folder 614)
  - Coe, Michael D. (Box 16, Folder 615)
  - Coffin, William Sloane (Box 16, Folder 616)
  - Coghill, R. D. (Box 16, Folder 617)
  - Cohane, Tim (Box 16, Folder 618)
  - Cohart, Edward M. (Box 16, Folder 619)
  - Cohen, Jerome A. (Box 16, Folder 620)
  - Cohen, Joy Ruth (Box 16, Folder 621)
  - Cohen, Melvin J. (Box 16, Folder 622)
  - Coker, Francis W. (Box 16, Folder 623)
  - Colbert, James W. Jr. (Box 16, Folder 624)
  - Cole, Douglas (Box 16, Folder 625)
  - Cole, Edward C. (Box 16, Folder 626)
  - Cole, Jack Westley (Box 16, Folder 627)
  - Cole, Tamie (Box 16, Folder 628)
  - Cole, Thomas A. (Box 16, Folder 629)
  - Coleman, John (Box 16, Folder 630)
  - Coleman, Kenneth R. (Box 16, Folder 631)
  - Collingnon, Jean H. (Box 16, Folder 632)
  - Collins, Leroy (Box 16, Folder 633)
  - Collins, William F. (Box 16, Folder 634)
  - Colton, Arthur W. (Box 16, Folder 635)
  - Columbo, Chris (Box 16, Folder 636)
  - Comer, G. P. (Box 16, Folder 637)
  - Comer, James Pierpont (Box 16, Folder 638)
  - Commager, Henry Steele (Box 16, Folder 639)
  - Conant, James B. (Box 16, Folder 640)
  - Conant, Lucy H. (Box 16, Folder 641)
  - Cone, Fairfax M. (Box 16, Folder 642)
  - Cone, Sydney M. (Box 16, Folder 643)
  - Conklin, Harold C. (Box 16, Folder 644)
  - Connelly, Marc (Box 16, Folder 645)
  - Connick, Louis Jr. (Box 16, Folder 646)
  - Conrad, Albert G. (Box 16, Folder 647)
  - Conroy, Rog (Box 16, Folder 648)
  - Conway, Edmund Virgil (Box 16, Folder 649)
  - Cook, Charles D. (Box 16, Folder 650)
  - Cook, Elmer J. (Box 16, Folder 651)
  - Cook, James W. (Box 16, Folder 652)
  - Cook, Robert (Box 16, Folder 653)
  - Cook, Robert Jay (Box 16, Folder 654)
  - Cooke, Joseph (Box 16, Folder 655)
  - Cooke, Michael G. (Box 16, Folder 656)
  - Cooke, Robert E. (M.D.) (Box 16, Folder 657)
  - Cooksey, Charlton (Box 16, Folder 658)
  - Coolidge, Robert T. (Box 16, Folder 659)
  - Coombe, Reginald G. (Box 17, Folder 660)
  - Cooper, Frank L. (Box 17, Folder 661)
  - Cooper, James W. (Box 17, Folder 662)
  - Cooper, John Sherman (Box 17, Folder 663)
  - Cooper, Richard N. (Box 17, Folder 664)
  - Corbett, Percy E. (Box 17, Folder 665)
  - Corbin, Arthur L. (Box 17, Folder 666)
  - Corcoran, D. (Box 17, Folder 667)
  - Cornell, W. Kenneth (Box 17, Folder 668)
  - Cornyn, William S. (Box 17, Folder 669-670)
  - Correa, Gustavo (Box 17, Folder 671)
  - Corrigan, Richard (Box 17, Folder 672)
  - Corso, Gragory (Box 17, Folder 673)
  - Corwinn, Robert N. (Box 17, Folder 674)
  - Costa-Gavras, Constantin (Box 17, Folder 675)
  - Costikyan, Clark W. Jr. (Box 17, Folder 676)
  - Costikyan, Granger (Box 17, Folder 677)
  - Cottrell, John T. (Box 17, Folder 678)
  - Countryman, Vern (Box 17, Folder 679)
  - Covell, Dexter O. Jr. (Box 17, Folder 680-681)
  - Cowan, Dean (Box 17, Folder 682)
  - Cowan, Michael (Box 17, Folder 683)
  - Cowan, Michael H. (Box 17, Folder 684)
  - Coward, Horace (Box 17, Folder 685)
  - Cowgill, George R. (Box 17, Folder 686)
  - Cowles, Alfred (Box 17, Folder 687)
  - Cowles, Philip B. (Box 17, Folder 688)
  - Cox. Archibald (Box 17, Folder 689)
  - Coxe, Macgrane (Box 17, Folder 690)
  - Cozza, Carmen (Box 17, Folder 691)
  - Craig, Clarence T. (Box 17, Folder 692)
  - Crane, Theodore (Box 17, Folder 693)
  - Crawford, Albert B. (Box 17, Folder 694)
  - Crawford, Jack Randall (Box 17, Folder 695)
  - Crelan, Edmund S. Jr. (Box 17, Folder 696)
  - Crelly, William R. (Box 17, Folder 697)
  - Cretella, Albert (Box 17, Folder 698)
  - Crocker, Richard L. (Box 17, Folder 699)
  - Crompton, Alfred W. (Box 17, Folder 700)
  - Cronyn, Hume (Box 17, Folder 701)
  - Crosby, Sumner M. (Box 17, Folder 702)
  - Cross, Wilbur Lucius (Box 18, Folder 703)
  - Crossley, F. R. Erskine (Box 18, Folder 704)
  - Crowder, Robert G. (Box 18, Folder 705)
  - Crowell, ------ (Box 18, Folder 706)
  - Crummey, Robert O. (Box 18, Folder 707)
  - Culler, A. Dwight (Box 18, Folder 708)
  - Culler, Dwight A. (Box 18, Folder 709)
  - Cullman, Howard S. (Box 18, Folder 710)
  - Cullman, Joseph F. (Box 18, Folder 711)
  - Cunningham, Wlater J. (Box 18, Folder 712)
  - Curnen, Edward C. Jr. (Box 18, Folder 713)
  - Curran, Peter F. (Box 18, Folder 714)
  - Curran, William E. (Box 18, Folder 715)
  - Currier, Donald (Box 18, Folder 716)
  - Curtin, Phyllis (Box 18, Folder 717)
  - Curtis, Lewis P. (Box 18, Folder 718)
  - Curtis, Mary E. (Box 18, Folder 719)
  - Curtiss, Joseph T. (Box 18, Folder 720)
  - Curts, Paul (Box 18, Folder 721)
  - Cushing, Harvey (Box 18, Folder 722)
  - Cushing, William Lee (Box 18, Folder 723)
  - Cutler, Carroll (Box 18, Folder 724)
  - Cutler, Lloyd A. (Box 18, Folder 725)
  - Cutler, Timothy (Box 18, Folder 726)
  - Cutter, Victor M. (Box 18, Folder 727)
  - Daggett, David (Box 18, Folder 728)
  - Daggett, Oliver E. (Box 18, Folder 729)
  - Daggett, William G. (Box 18, Folder 730)
  - Dahl, ------ (Box 18, Folder 731)
  - Dahl, George (Box 18, Folder 732)
  - Dahl, Nils Alstrup (Box 18, Folder 733)
  - Dahl, Robert A. (Box 18, Folder 734)
  - Dale, Howie (Box 18, Folder 735)
  - Dallin, Alexander (Box 18, Folder 736)
  - Daly, Radley H. (Box 18, Folder 737)
  - Dalzell, Robert F. Jr. (Box 18, Folder 738)
  - D'Amico, Michael (Box 18, Folder 739)
  - Dana, Edwrd S. (Box 18, Folder 740)
  - Dana, James D. (Box 18, Folder 741)
  - Danby, John M. A. (Box 18, Folder 742)
  - Danelski, David J. (Box 18, Folder 743)
  - Danes, Gibson A. (Box 18, Folder 744-745)
  - Danforth, John C. (Box 19, Folder 746)
  - Dangler, David Waller (Box 19, Folder 747)
  - Daniels, Charles B. (Box 19, Folder 748)
  - Daniels, John C. (Box 19, Folder 749)
  - D'Arcy, ------- (Box 19, Folder 750)
  - Darling, Arthur B. (Box 19, Folder 751)
  - Darling, George B. (Box 19, Folder 752)
  - Darlington, Paul E. (Box 19, Folder 753)
  - Darnell, ----- (Box 19, Folder 754)
  - Darrow, Daniel (Box 19, Folder 755)
  - Dasey, Miriam K. (Box 19, Folder 756)
  - Davenny, Ward (Box 19, Folder 757)
  - Davenport, John (Box 19, Folder 758)
  - Davenport, William H. (Box 19, Folder 759)
  - David, Worth (Box 19, Folder 760)
  - Davidovits, Paul (Box 19, Folder 761)
  - Davidson, Eugene A. (Box 19, Folder 762)
  - Davidson, Robert B. (Box 19, Folder 763)
  - Davie, James S. (Box 19, Folder 764)
  - Davie, Maurice R. (Box 19, Folder 765)
  - Davis, Charles T. and Jeanne Curtis Davis (Box 19, Folder 766)
  - Davis, Clarence C. (Box 19, Folder 767)
  - Davis, David B. (Box 19, Folder 768)
  - Davis, Elmer (Box 19, Folder 769)
  - Davis, Jeanne Curtis (Box 19, Folder 770)
  - Davis, Jerome (Box 19, Folder 771)
  - Davis, Kenneth P. (Box 19, Folder 772)
  - Davis, Lanny J. (Box 19, Folder 773)
  - Davis, Margaret Bryan (Box 19, Folder 774)
  - Davis, Morris S. (Box 19, Folder 775)
  - Davis, Renee (Box 19, Folder 776)
  - Davis, True (Box 19, Folder 777)
  - Davison, Endicott P. (Box 19, Folder 778)
  - Davison, F. Trubee (Box 19, Folder 779)
  - Dawson, Christopher M. (Box 19, Folder 780)
  - Day, Arthur L. (Box 19, Folder 781)
  - Day, Clayton (Box 19, Folder 782)
  - Day, Clive (Box 19, Folder 783)
  - Day, Gardiner M. (Box 19, Folder 784)
  - Day, George Edward (Box 19, Folder 785)
  - Day, George Parmly (Box 20, Folder 786)
  - Day, Jeremiah (Box 20, Folder 787)
  - Day, Lincoln (Box 20, Folder 788)
  - Day, Philip S. (Box 20, Folder 789)
  - Day, Ruth (Box 20, Folder 790)
  - Day, Theodore (Box 20, Folder 791)
  - Dayan, Yael (Box 20, Folder 792)
  - Debreu, Gerard (Box 20, Folder 793)
  - DeCanio, Stephen (Box 20, Folder 794)
  - deCernea, Edward (Box 20, Folder 795)
  - Dedijer, Stevan (Box 20, Folder 796)
  - Deevey, Edward S. Jr. (Box 20, Folder 797)
  - De Forest, Gideon K. (Box 20, Folder 798)
  - De Forest, H. S. (Box 20, Folder 799)
  - De Forest, Lee (Box 20, Folder 800)
  - Delano, William (Box 20, Folder 801)
  - Delevoryas, Theodore (Box 20, Folder 802)
  - Delgado, Jose (M.D.) (Box 20, Folder 803)
  - Delgass, N. Nicholas (Box 20, Folder 804)
  - Dellinger, David (Box 20, Folder 805)
  - Dellums, Ron (Box 20, Folder 806)
  - De Loache, Benjamin (Box 20, Folder 807)
  - Delsolar, Charlotte (Box 20, Folder 808)
  - Deluca, Louis S. (Box 20, Folder 809)
  - Demarque, Pierre Raymond (Box 20, Folder 810)
  - Demetz, Peter (Box 20, Folder 811)
  - Deming, Barbara (Box 20, Folder 812)
  - Dempsey, John (Box 20, Folder 813)
  - Denison, George A. (Box 20, Folder 814)
  - Denker, David D. (Box 20, Folder 815)
  - Denny, Frederick M. (Box 20, Folder 816)
  - Denslow, Herbert M. (Box 20, Folder 817)
  - D'Entreves, Alexander P. (Box 20, Folder 818)
  - Depew, Chauncey M. (Box 20, Folder 819-820)
  - Dession, George (Box 20, Folder 821)
  - De Terra, H. (Box 20, Folder 822)
  - Detweiler, A. Henry (Box 20, Folder 823)
  - Deutsch, Jan G. (Box 20, Folder 824)
  - Deutsch, Karl W. (Box 20, Folder 825)
  - Deutsch, Morton (Box 20, Folder 826)
  - De Vane, P. Cameron (Box 20, Folder 827)
  - De Vane, William C. (Box 20, Folder 828)
  - De Vane, William S. (Box 21, Folder 829)
  - de Varona, Donna (Box 21, Folder 830)
  - Dewolf, Maurice M. (Box 21, Folder 831)
  - Dexter, Franklin B. (Box 21, Folder 832)
  - Dexter, Franklin B. and Mrs. Dexter (Box 21, Folder 833)
  - Dibbell, ----- (Box 21, Folder 834)
  - Dicke, Charles D. (Box 21, Folder 835)
  - Dickerson, Edwin (Box 21, Folder 836)
  - Dickey, Charles D. (Box 21, Folder 837)
  - Dickinson, Fred E. (Box 21, Folder 838)
  - Dickoff, James W. (Box 21, Folder 839)
  - Dickson, Janet M. (Box 21, Folder 840)
  - Diedrickson, Theodore (Box 21, Folder 841)
  - Diers, Donna Kaye (Box 21, Folder 842)
  - Dietrich, Harold (Box 21, Folder 843)
  - Dillon, C. Douglas (Box 21, Folder 844)
  - Dilworth, J. Richardson (Box 21, Folder 845)
  - Dimock, George E. Jr. (Box 21, Folder 846)
  - Dimond, Albert E. (Box 21, Folder 847)
  - Dinkler, Erich (Box 21, Folder 848)
  - Dionne, Roger (Box 21, Folder 849)
  - Dirks, H. Edward (Box 21, Folder 850)
  - Dirkson, Everett and Louella Dirkson (Box 21, Folder 851)
  - Dittes, James E. (Box 21, Folder 852)
  - Dix, Robert H. (Box 21, Folder 853)
  - Dixon, ----- (Box 21, Folder 854)
  - Dixon, Owen (Box 21, Folder 855)
  - Dobby, Ernest H. G. (Box 21, Folder 856)
  - Dobie, Albert R. (Box 21, Folder 857)
  - Dobihal, Edward F. (Box 21, Folder 858)
  - Doble, Enoch H. (Box 21, Folder 859)
  - Dobzhansky, Theodore (Box 21, Folder 860)
  - Dodd, ------ (Box 21, Folder 861)
  - Dodd, Lee Wilson (Box 21, Folder 862)
  - Dodd, Norman (Box 21, Folder 863)
  - Dodd, Thomas V. (Box 21, Folder 864)
  - Dodge, Barnett F. (Box 21, Folder 865)
  - Dodge, Marshall Jr. (Box 21, Folder 866)
  - Dodge, Raymond (Box 21, Folder 867)
  - Doering, William Von E. (Box 21, Folder 868)
  - Dole, William C. (Box 21, Folder 869)
  - Dollard, John (Box 21, Folder 870)
  - Domen, Toyonobu (Box 22, Folder 871)
  - Dominick, Peter (Box 22, Folder 872)
  - Dominquez, George (Box 22, Folder 873)
  - Domres, Marty (Box 22, Folder 874)
  - Donahue, Fran (Box 22, Folder 875)
  - Donaldson, E. Talbot (Box 22, Folder 876)
  - Donaldson, Norman C. (Box 22, Folder 877)
  - Donaldson, William H. (Box 22, Folder 878)
  - Donelli, Buff (Box 22, Folder 879)
  - Donham, William (Box 22, Folder 880)
  - Donleavy, J. P. (Box 22, Folder 881)
  - Donleavy, John H. (Box 22, Folder 882)
  - Donnelley, Gaylord (Box 22, Folder 883)
  - Donnelly, Richard C. (Box 22, Folder 884)
  - Donner, Fred M. (Box 22, Folder 885)
  - Donnor, Frank (Box 22, Folder 886)
  - Donovan, Hedley (Box 22, Folder 887)
  - Donovan, Richard F. (Box 22, Folder 888)
  - Doob, Leonard W. (Box 22, Folder 889)
  - Dorius, Raymond J. (Box 22, Folder 890)
  - Dos Passos, John (Box 22, Folder 891)
  - Dougherty, Raymond P. (Box 22, Folder 892)
  - Douglas, Kenneth N. (Box 22, Folder 893)
  - Douglas, Paul (Box 22, Folder 894)
  - Douglas, William W. (Box 22, Folder 895)
  - Dove, Kenley (Box 22, Folder 896)
  - Dowd, Rachael (Box 22, Folder 897)
  - Downs, Wilbur G. (Box 22, Folder 898)
  - Doyle, Robert J. (Box 22, Folder 899)
  - Dreibholz, Ursula (Box 22, Folder 900)
  - Drew, James M. (Box 22, Folder 901)
  - Driver, Cecil H. (Box 22, Folder 902)
  - Du Bois, Augustus J. (Box 22, Folder 903)
  - Dubridge, ----- (Box 22, Folder 904)
  - Dudley, Samuel W. (Box 22, Folder 905)
  - Dudman, Robert (Box 22, Folder 906)
  - Duff, Raymond S. (Box 22, Folder 907)
  - Duffy, Joseph (Box 22, Folder 908)
  - Dugan, Allen (Box 22, Folder 909)
  - Duggan, ----- (Box 22, Folder 910)
  - Duke, Stephen B. (Box 22, Folder 911)
  - Dulang, George W. Jr. (Box 22, Folder 912)
  - Dulles, Allen W. (Box 22, Folder 913)
  - Dumas, Rhetaugh G. (Box 22, Folder 914)
  - Dun, Angus (Box 22, Folder 915)
  - Dunbar, Carl O. (Box 22, Folder 916)
  - Duncan, ----- (Box 22, Folder 917)
  - Duncan, Robert (Box 22, Folder 918)
  - Dunoombe, David (Box 22, Folder 919)
  - Dunford, Nelson (Box 22, Folder 920)
  - Dunham, Clarence W. (Box 22, Folder 921)
  - Dunham, Lawrence B. Jr. (Box 23, Folder 922)
  - Dunham, William H. Jr. (Box 23, Folder 923)
  - Dunlap, Elliott (Box 23, Folder 924)
  - Dunn, Frederick S. (Box 23, Folder 925)
  - Dunn, Kempton (Box 23, Folder 926)
  - Dunning, Harrison F. (Box 23, Folder 927)
  - Duran, Manuel (Box 23, Folder 928)
  - Duran-Reynals, Francisco (Box 23, Folder 929)
  - Durfee, Edward L. (Box 23, Folder 930)
  - Durgin, Russell L. (Box 23, Folder 931)
  - Duryee, William R. (Box 23, Folder 932)
  - Dutcher, Judson S. (Box 23, Folder 933)
  - Dutton, Henry S. (Box 23, Folder 934-935)
  - Dutton, Samuel W. S. (Box 23, Folder 936)
  - Duval, Richard Paul (Box 23, Folder 937)
  - Dwight, Timothy, 1769 (Box 23, Folder 938)
  - Dwight, Timothy, 1849 (Box 23, Folder 939)
  - Dwight, William T. (Box 23, Folder 940)
  - Dworkin, Ronald M. (Box 23, Folder 941)
  - Dwyer, Martin Jr. (Box 23, Folder 942)
  - Dye, Mary C. (Box 23, Folder 943)
  - Dyen, Isidore (Box 23, Folder 944)
  - Eaton, Daniel C. (Box 23, Folder 945)
  - Eaton, George F. (Box 23, Folder 946)
  - Eaton, Richard (Box 23, Folder 947)
  - Eaton, Walter Prichard (Box 23, Folder 948)
  - Eban, Abba (Box 23, Folder 949)
  - Ebbert, Arthur Jr. (Box 23, Folder 950)
  - Eberhard, Robert G. (Box 23, Folder 951)
  - Eckle, John N. (Box 23, Folder 952)
  - Ecklund, John E. (Box 23, Folder 953)
  - Edelstein, Teri (Box 23, Folder 954)
  - Edgerly, C. T. (Box 23, Folder 955)
  - Edgerton, Franklin (Box 24, Folder 956)
  - Edgerton, Malcolm J. Jr. (Box 24, Folder 957)
  - Edmonds, John (Box 24, Folder 958)
  - Edmonds, Edwin (Box 24, Folder 959)
  - Edwards Donald (Box 24, Folder 960)
  - Edwards, Herbert (Box 24, Folder 961)
  - Edwards, Jonathan (Box 24, Folder 962)
  - Edwards, Jonathan Jr. (Box 24, Folder 963)
  - Edwards, Thomas K. (Box 24, Folder 964)
  - Egan, Margarita (Box 24, Folder 965)
  - Ehrlich, ----- (Box 24, Folder 966)
  - Ehrmann, Jacques (Box 24, Folder 967)
  - Einhorn, Joe (Box 24, Folder 968)
  - Eiseley, Loren (Box 24, Folder 969)
  - Eisenhower, Dwight D. (Box 24, Folder 970)
  - Eisenhower, Milton (Box 24, Folder 971)
  - Eisenman, Alvin (Box 24, Folder 972)
  - Elagin, Ivan (Box 24, Folder 973)
  - Eldridge, Azariah (Box 24, Folder 974)
  - Elfrey, Priscilla R. (Box 24, Folder 975)
  - Elgart, Larry (Box 24, Folder 976)
  - Eliot, T. S. (Box 24, Folder 977)
  - Elkin, W. L. (Box 24, Folder 978)
  - Ellender, Allen J. E. (Box 24, Folder 979)
  - Ellington, Duke (Box 24, Folder 980)
  - Elliot, Nellie P. (Box 24, Folder 981)
  - Elliot, Richard M. (Box 24, Folder 982)
  - Ellis, H. M. (Box 24, Folder 983)
  - Ellmann, Richard (Box 24, Folder 984)
  - Ellsberg, Daniel (Box 24, Folder 985)
  - Ellsworth, ----- (Box 24, Folder 986)
  - Ellsworth, John S. Jr. (Box 24, Folder 987)
  - Ellsworth, Oliver (Box 24, Folder 988)
  - Ellsworth, William (Box 24, Folder 989)
  - Elwood, Craig (Box 24, Folder 990)
  - Embersits, John F. (Box 24, Folder 991)
  - Embree, Edwinn R. (Box 24, Folder 992)
  - Embree, John F. (Box 24, Folder 993)
  - Embree, William (Box 24, Folder 994)
  - Emerson, J. Y. (Box 24, Folder 995)
  - Emerson, Thomas. (Box 24, Folder 996)
  - Emerson, William R. (Box 24, Folder 997)
  - Enders, Ostrom (Box 24, Folder 998)
  - Endleman, Marian Wright (Box 24, Folder 999)
  - Engelhardt, Frederick (Box 24, Folder 1000)
  - Engley, Donald B. (Box 24, Folder 1001)
  - English, James (Box 24, Folder 1002)
  - Engman, Robert M. (Box 24, Folder 1003)
  - Engstrom, H. G. (Box 24, Folder 1004)
  - Enke, Stephen (Box 24, Folder 1005)
  - Epstein, ----- (Box 24, Folder 1006)
  - Epstein, Franklin H. (M.D.) (Box 24, Folder 1007)
  - Erickson, Kai T. (Box 24, Folder 1008-09)
  - Erle, Broadus (Box 24, Folder 1010)
  - Erlich, Richard (Box 24, Folder 1011)
  - Erlich, Victor (Box 24, Folder 1012)
  - Ermoyan, Suren H. (Box 24, Folder 1013)
  - Eron, Leonard D. (Box 24, Folder 1014)
  - Esler, Lemist (Box 24, Folder 1015)
  - Espy, Robert G. (Box 25, Folder 1016)
  - Estoclet, Emil E. Jr. (Box 25, Folder 1017)
  - Eusden, John D. (Box 25, Folder 1018)
  - Evang, Karl (Box 25, Folder 1019)
  - Evans, Alexander W. (Box 25, Folder 1020)
  - Evans, Alfred Spring (Box 25, Folder 1021)
  - Evans, Theodore S. (Box 25, Folder 1022)
  - Evans, Walker (Box 25, Folder 1023)
  - Evarts, John M. (Box 25, Folder 1024)
  - Evarts, William M. (Box 25, Folder 1025)
  - Everett, ----- (Box 25, Folder 1026)
  - Everett, Ralph H. (Box 25, Folder 1027)
  - Evers, Charles (Box 25, Folder 1028)
  - Ewald, Philip (Box 25, Folder 1029)
  - Ewell, John W. (Box 25, Folder 1030)
  - Eyre, Lawrence Lee (Box 25, Folder 1031)
  - Fabian, Richard G. (Box 25, Folder 1032)
  - Fackenheim, Emil L. (Box 25, Folder 1033)
  - Fagan, Peter J. (Box 25, Folder 1034)
  - Fairbank, Henry A. (Box 25, Folder 1035)
  - Fairchild, Fred Rogers (Box 25, Folder 1036)
  - Fairfield, Herb (Box 25, Folder 1037)
  - Falb, Lewis (Box 25, Folder 1038)
  - Falk, Isadore Sydney (Box 25, Folder 1039)
  - Fall, Bernard B. (Box 25, Folder 1040)
  - Fanton, Jonathon F. (Box 25, Folder 1041)
  - Farmer, James (Box 25, Folder 1042)
  - Farnam, Charles H. (Box 25, Folder 1043)
  - Farnam, Henry W. (Box 25, Folder 1044)
  - Farnam, Thomas W. (Box 25, Folder 1045)
  - Farnham, Charles S. (Box 25, Folder 1046)
  - Farr, Hollon A. (Box 25, Folder 1047)
  - Farrell, R. Barry (Box 25, Folder 1048)
  - Faulk, John Henry (Box 25, Folder 1049)
  - Faulkner, Dewey R. (Box 25, Folder 1050)
  - Faunce, William H. P. (Box 25, Folder 1051)
  - Faure, Edgar (Box 25, Folder 1052)
  - Fayen, George (Box 25, Folder 1053)
  - Feddie, Norman A. (Box 25, Folder 1054)
  - Fedson, ----- (Box 25, Folder 1055)
  - Fegan, Joseph C. Hr. (Box 25, Folder 1056)
  - Feidelson, Charl4es Hr. (Box 25, Folder 1057)
  - Feinstein, Alvan R. (Box 25, Folder 1058)
  - Feit, Walter (Box 25, Folder 1059)
  - Feldman, Walter S. (Box 25, Folder 1060)
  - Fellner, William J. (Box 25, Folder 1061)
  - Fenn, Henry C. (Box 25, Folder 1062)
  - Fenn, John Bennett (Box 25, Folder 1063)
  - Fenton, Charles A. (Box 26, Folder 1064)
  - Ferguson, Alan D. (Box 26, Folder 1065)
  - Ferguson, Maynard (Box 26, Folder 1066)
  - Ferld, Roger A. (Box 26, Folder 1067)
  - Ferry, Orris S. (Box 26, Folder 1068)
  - Fesler, James W. (Box 26, Folder 1069)
  - Fetter, Robert B. (Box 26, Folder 1070)
  - Field, F. Bernice (Box 26, Folder 1071)
  - Fields, Curtis (Box 26, Folder 1072)
  - Finch, Stuart C. (Box 26, Folder 1073)
  - Findlay, John N. (Box 26, Folder 1074)
  - Fink, Seymour M. (Box 26, Folder 1075)
  - Finkelstein, Dorothee M. (Box 26, Folder 1076)
  - Finkelstein, Jacob H. (Box 26, Folder 1077)
  - Finletter, Thomas (Box 26, Folder 1078)
  - Fischer, Henry (Box 26, Folder 1079)
  - Fischoff, Ephraim (Box 26, Folder 1080)
  - Fisher, Alex M. (Box 26, Folder 1081)
  - Fisher, George P. (Box 26, Folder 1082)
  - Fisher, Irving (Box 26, Folder 1083)
  - Fisher, Irving N. (Box 26, Folder 1084)
  - Fisher, James J. (Box 26, Folder 1085)
  - Fisher, Ralph T. (Box 26, Folder 1086)
  - Fisher, Samuel H. (Box 26, Folder 1087)
  - Fishlow, Albert (Box 26, Folder 1088)
  - Fishman, Joelle (Box 26, Folder 1089)
  - Fitch, Charles H. (Box 26, Folder 1090)
  - Fitch, Eleazer T. (Box 26, Folder 1091)
  - Fitch, Frederic B. (Box 26, Folder 1092)
  - Fitch, Odonnel (Box 26, Folder 1093)
  - Fitt, Alfred (Box 26, Folder 1094)
  - Fitts, Dudley (Box 26, Folder 1095)
  - Fitzgerald, Edmond (Box 26, Folder 1096)
  - Fixman, Marshall (Box 26, Folder 1097)
  - Flack, Roberta (Box 26, Folder 1098)
  - Flagg, Amos Alonzo (Box 26, Folder 1099)
  - Fleck, Stephen (Box 26, Folder 1100)
  - Fleishman, Edwin A. (Box 26, Folder 1101)
  - Fleishman, Joel L. (Box 26, Folder 1102)
  - Fleming, Donald (Box 26, Folder 1103)
  - Felming, Sarah (Box 26, Folder 1104)
  - Flint, Richard F. (Box 26, Folder 1105)